You're both involved with Japan Plati?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb.
I saw Misaki talking with you guys.
Weren't you at the company visiting Kotobuki?
Well, the cat's out of the bag now.
They're founders.
Those two founded Japan Plati.
What?
Neiru! You changed your look?
I'll stop if it's weird.
No, stay this way.
I knew you had it in you.
Yeah. You look like a lady.
Or maybe a princess.
Here.
Who're they?
Right is Acca. Left is Ura-Acca.
For real? Acca's totally hot.
And me?
Like a bad apple.
Hey...
So, they were both human?
We still are.
We abandoned our bodies and kept just our brains.
What? Gross!
Once young scientific geniuses, now just dummies.
Well, I'm sure you have a lot of questions, but—
Oh, it's from Momo.
Leaving us on read?
She got asked out?!
By a girl again, right?
A boy?!
Hey, let's go up!
Yeah!
All right.
Girls' talk! Girls' talk!
Didn't they have questions for us?
Girls' talk takes priority.
Oh! Momo!
Oh, you changed your hairstyle.
I did.
You seem different today yourself, Momoe.
Yeah.
Do I?
Oh, who cares? Tell us the rest!
Oh, right.
Today, I went on a date.
Where'd you meet him?! You go to a girls' school.
He's my follower. And the first time we met...
he told me.
Told you what?
H-He asked me out.
Lucky.
But it's over! There won't be a next time.
What?!
Why?
Was he different on the date?
No.
It was the first time a guy ever asked me out,
so I dressed as girly as I could.
Bare legs and stuff.
And when I got to the meeting place,
he looked horrified.
Horrified? What for?
He thought I was a boy.
So, that's the funny thing that happened to me.
We can't laugh at that.
Laugh. I'll feel worse otherwise.
Oh, here's lunch. I made my specialty, so eat up.
Excuse me.
What's wrong, Ohto?
Is it true you're quitting your job here?
Yes. I think I've figured out a way
to make a living as an artist.
You're not running away?
Running?
Nothing.
Ohto...
I'm going to hold a small solo exhibition.
Come see it if you like.
What should I do, Leon?
Panic,
are you a boy
or a girl?
It must be nice, not judging by appearance.
I wish I could be with someone I like.
Veni!
I'm Kurita Kaoru.
You sound...
Oh well, it'd be embarrassing to talk more feminine.
Don't worry, you look plenty feminine.
Or are you playing up the contrast?
What's your name?
I'm... Sawaki Momotaro.
Well, call me whatever.
Momo?
Momoko?
Momoe?
Momoko!
Momoe.
Tall, cool beauties like you are totally my type.
Oh okay, I get it.
You don't care if I'm a girl.
Just like Haruka.
Haruka?
She's a girl, but she said she loves me.
So, a lesbian?
I'm not like that.
You're not?
Inside...
I'm a boy.
Huh?
That crocodile's something else.
Thank you, Panic.
Come here.
So, his name's Panic.
Are you full?
The hell is this?!
Are you okay, Kaoru?
I wanted to see you, Kaoru!
No!
Let go!
You're so cute and fair.
Almost too fragile to hug.
What idiot could believe that you're a boy "on the inside"?!
Kaoru!
Momoe!
Are you after Kaoru, too?!
Who is this guy?
My kendo club advisor.
I went to him for advice.
I thought he was a good teacher,
but he pushed me down in the boardinghouse and...
I... got pregnant.
I felt bad for the baby, but I...
I...
You don't have to say anymore!
I'm strong!
So am I!
You won his trust, then exploited him.
I hate cowards like you more than anyone.
You're after Kaoru too, aren't you?!
I'll stab you and your disgusting jealousy!
I'll get you out.
Who said you could get on top of me?!
I'll kill any man who makes passes at my Kaoru.
I'll cut off the legs they walk on
and the mouths they talk with!
How's Momo? Is she all right?
You're always worrying about other people,
but if you don't focus on your
own fight, you'll get tripped up.
I know that!
I know that, but...
Or do you do it to avoid thinking about your own problems?
It's all because a painting I did here won a prize.
The one of Koito?
It's all the way in the back.
I really want you to see it.
Have some confidence, Kaoru!
You're the cutest girl I've ever seen.
I'm...
I'm a boy.
I'm a boy...
And...
I'm...
a girl!
This is it.
What?
Get lost!
Jump!
Magnificent!
I want to teach you all over again!
Next time I'm reborn, I'll be the one to protect you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Not all girls want to be protected.
Yeah? Sorry.
What about you?
I don't get a choice about it.
Of course you do.
You're a lovely girl.
And you're a brave boy.
Thanks.
You mind younger guys?
It depends how much younger.
Let me make a reservation.
Don't get a boyfriend until I see you again.
A what?
Kaoru—
Shh!
What's going on?
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Haruka?
Momoe?
Huh?
But her statue's gone.
It's over.
It's really over!
Momoe won't be coming anymore.
Huh?
She cleared the game?
Exactly.
Work hard so that you can follow in her footsteps.
Meaning Momoe got out first?
She could have told us.
I agree.
Sorry! I remembered something I have to do after all!
I've got to go!
What do you mean, "after all"?
See you, then.
Wanna go for ramen?
Sure.
I'm home!
Where are you going, Ai?
It's getting late.
Just... stuff with everyone.
Everyone?
Everyone.
Okay.
Make sure you message me every 30 minutes.
Yup. I'm off.
Me—
No, it's different?
It's you.
But you, grown up.
It's me... grown up?
Don't you think it looks like someone?
My mom.
Yes.
Someday, you'll be a wonderful,
adult woman like your mother.
Kind, strong, and beautiful.
You love my mom, don't you?
Yes. With all my heart.
You're her daughter...
so you should have faith in yourself.
Mr. Sawaki...
Yes?
There's something I want to ask you.
Why did Koito die?
Our plans may end up going off-course.
Looks like it.
To confront Thanatos, we need
warriors of Eros, his polar opposite.
Will Momoe go back there for us?
No clue.
She knows it now.
The overwhelming fear of death.
Bad girl.
I'll tell teacher on you.
Congratulations. You completed your mission.
That girl came back to life.
Veni!
I'd like to let you go.
Out of respect for the way you've
risked your life for friendship.
But you see, Frill will get mad at me if she finds out.
Frill?
This is a pain, so I'll cut to the chase.
Do you want to die here?
Well, I figured.
Panic...
In that case, I guess I'll settle for this thing.
They say crocodile tastes like chicken.
Have some, too.
Are you all right, Momo?
I can't sleep. I can't sleep.
I can't
sleep. I can't sleep. I can't sleep.
I can't sleep. I can't sleep.
To be continued.